Guide to The Billie Jean King Collection 1901-2019 (bulk, 1940-2019) MS 3147
New-York Historical Society
- Series VII. Print matter, 1901-2020 (bulk, 1940-2020); 19 Linear feet in 14 record cartons, 4 flat boxes, and various oversize folders
  - Subseries VII.D. Books, 1943-2019; 3.5 Linear feet in 4 record cartons
    - Evansville Area Tennis Patrons. Serve it Up, 1982 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 1)
      Recipe book printed by the Evansville Area Tennis Patrons with recipes contributed by tennis pros and friends of the organization, including a recipe for oatmeal pineapple cookies from BJK. Includes an inserted letter to BJK and newspaper clipping.
    - Finder, Robert L., Jr. The Financial Professional's Guide to Communication, 2013 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 2)
    - The Freedom Writers Foundation. Freedom Writers Foundation, 2004 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 3)
      Includes inscription to BJK and Ilana Kloss from "Erin."
    - Friedman, Steward D. Leading the Life You Want, 2014 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 4)
      Includes inserted letter to BJK from author.
    - Frist, Karyn McLaughlin. Love You, Daddy Boy: Daughters Honor the Fathers They Love, 2006 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 5)
      Includes inscription to BJK from author.
    - Gillibrand, Kirsten. Off the Sidelines, 2014 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 13)
    - Glangchai, Cristal. Venture Girls, 2018 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 14)
    - Graham, Laura. Sports Bear: A Day at the Tennis Court, 2004 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 6)
    - Guerrant, Anne. How to be Richer Than Your Parents, 2016 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 7)
      Contains inscription to BJK and Ilana Kloss from author.
    - HCCTA Elementary Reads. Champion Citizen, 2011 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 8)
      Contains books created by Hamilton County Community Tennis Association Elementary Reads on inspirational athletes, including BJK, Arthur Ashe, James Blake, Gale Sayers, and George Taliaferro. Each signed by author and HCCTA Elementary Reads creator and writing producer.
    - Hoffman, Greg. The Art of World Team Tennis, 1977 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 9)
    - Jackman, Michele with Susan Waggoner. Star Teams, Key Players, 1991 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 10)
    - John, Elton. Anthology and It's A Little Bit Funny, 1977, 1985 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 11)
      Includes Elton John's Anthology book of sheet music 1985 and It's a Little Bit Funny 1977.
    - John, Elton. Love is the Cure: On Life, Loss, and the End of AIDS, 2012 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 12)
    - Johnson, David. Voice of Beauty: A Photographic Celebration of African Women, 2009 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 13)
    - Katz, Larry. Beyond Winning, 2010 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 14)
      Contains inscription to BJK by author.
    - Katz, Naomi. Beautiful: Being an Empowered Young Woman, 2016 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 15)
    - King, Billie Jean with Kim Chapin. Billie Jean, 1975 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 15)
    - Klainer, Pamela York. How Much is Enough?, 2002 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 16)
    - Knight, J.J. Nothing Ventured, 2007 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 17)
    - Kovacs, Mark S., E. Paul Roetert, and Todd S. Ellenbecker with USTA. Complete Conditioning for Tennis, 2016 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 1)
      Includes inscription to BJK from Mark Kovacs.
    - Kusama, Yayoi. Recent Works, 1996 September 17-October 19 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 2)
      Exhibition catalog from the Robert Miller Gallery.
    - Litman, Bob. Live the Best Story of Your Life, 2016 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 3)
      Includes inserted note to BJK from author.
    - Macci, Rick with Jim Martz. Macci Magic: Extracting Greatness from Yourself and Others, 2013 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 4)
    - Marloe, Wendy and Joanna Chen. Sanctuary, 2015 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 5)
      Includes inserted letter to BJK from publisher.
    - Meltzer, Brad. I am Billie Jean King (1 of 2 copies), 2019 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 6A)
    - Meltzer, Brad. I am Billie Jean King (2 of 2 copies), 2019 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 16)
    - Momentum. TED Women, 2015 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 17)
    - Morse, A.R. Tennis Champion: Billie Jean King, 1976 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 6B)
    - Mundy, Liza. The Richer Sex, 2012 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 7)
    - Northup, Fred. Winning More than the Game, 2012 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 8)
    - Peters, Lisa Gaskill. Doris E. Coppock: Renaissance Woman at McPherson College, 2017 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 9)
    - Piccinini, Patricia. Nature's Little Helpers, 2005 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 10)
    - Potter, Edward C. (ed). USLTA Official Tennis Yearbook and Guide, 1960, 1961 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 11)
    - Powers, Debbie Millbern. Meeting Her Match, 2014 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 12)
    - Prudden, Bonnie. After Fifty Fitness Guide, 2011 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 13)
    - Prudden, Bonnie. Myotherapy, 2010 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 14)
    - Rennert, Rick. Open Season 2006: A Legendary Showcase (Offsite-box 43, Folder 6)
    - Rennert, Rick. Unmatched: The Spectacular Showcase of the US Open, 2012 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 15)
    - Roth, Patrick A. The End of Back Pain, 2014 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 16)
      Inscribed to BJK.
    - Ruiz, Don Miguel. The Four Agreements, 1997 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 17)
      Includes inserted fan letter sent to BJK along with this book and Marguerite de Angeli's The Door in the Wall.
    - Sarg, Tony. Baby's Book, 1943 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 18)
    - Schatz, Kate. Rad American Women A-Z, 2015 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 1)
    - Serure, Pamela. Dear Heart: Life-saving Stories from Women to Women, 2009 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 2)
      File includes additional printed material and DVD sent to BJK from events of the heart.
    - Snyder, Benjamin. The History of World TeamTennis: Over Forty Years of Courting Equality, 2017 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 3)
    - Special Olympics. Tennis Coaching Quick Start Guide, 2006 March (Offsite-box 39, Folder 4)
    - Tobias, Andrew. The Best Little Boy in the World Grows Up, 1998 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 18)
    - Virginia Slims Circuit. Virginia Slims Media Guide, 1977 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 5)
    - Willenson, Neil. A Journey of Hope: Inspiring Stories of Courage and Unconditional Love, 2005 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 6)
      Includes inscription from author to BJK and additional printed materials from Camp Heartland.
    - Williams, Dell and Lynn Vannucci. Revolution in the Garden: Memoirs of the Gardenkeeper, 2005 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 7)
    - Williams, Owen. Ahead of the Game, 2013 November (Offsite-box 39, Folder 8)
      Contains author signature.
    - Woolard, Edgar. Dear Caroline, Dear Will, 2005 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 9)
      Inscribed by author to Ilana Kloss.
    - Woolum, Janet. Outstanding Women Athletes, 1992 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 10)
    - Worden, Minky. The Unfinished Revolution (2 folders), 2012 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 11-12)
      Includes 2 copies of book, each inscribed to BJK by author, letters from author, and printed material from Human Rights Watch.
  - Subseries VII.E. Ephemera, 1901-2018 (bulk, 1960-2018); 1 Linear feet in 1 record carton and oversize folders
    Subseries VII.E includes ephemeral paper material, the majority of which are single items that were not initially stored with a particular record group. Types of items include artworks given to BJK, autographs, event tickets, and formerly framed magazine covers.
    - Barnard sketch copy, 1998 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 13)
      Contains photocopy of BJK sketch by artist D. Barnard signed by artist and BJK.
    - BJK American Express subway ad postcard, 2000 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 28)
      Immediate Source of Acquisition
      Donated by photographer June Harrison in 2019.
      Signed by BJK and photographer June Harrison.
    - BJK autographs, undated (Offsite-box 39, Folder 14)
    - BJK bumper sticker, circa 1960s-1970s (Offsite-box 43, Folder 7)
    - BJK caricature pencil drawing, 2003 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 5)
      BJK caricature pencil drawing mounted on board given to BJK by the WTA tour in thanks and acknowledgement of their 30th Anniversary celebration.
    - BJK fact sheet, circa 1980 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 15)
    - BJK mounted autograph and photo [removed from frame], undated (Offsite-box 43, Folder 8)
    - BJK quotations, undated (Offsite-box 60, Folder 6)
      Laminated quarter-fold sheet with four BJK quotations. Quotations are "I have often been asked whether I am a woman or an athlete. The question is absurd. I am an athlete. I am a woman."; "I think self-awareness is probably the most important thing toward being a champion."; "You know, I still wake up some mornings thinking I haven't played the match yet."; and "Balance is the key to both sports and life."
    - BJK unsent postcards, circa 1970s (Offsite-box 39, Folder 16)
    - Bobby Riggs' bridge jump certificate, circa 1973 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 17)
      Ticket with text: "If I lose to Billie Jean King, I will jump off a bridge." Bobby Riggs. THIS CERTIFICATE ADMITS ONE PERSON TO THE BOBBY RIGGS' BRIDGE JUMP. Place, time and date to be determined. Odds that Riggs will try to con the bridge into lowering itself before the jump are 8 to 5.
    - Bruce Lattig BJK painting, circa 1980s (Offsite-box 61, Folder 1)
    - Bumper sticker, 2004 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 18)
      Bumper sticker reading "Well-behaved women seldom make history - Laurel Thatcher Ulrich."
    - Elizabeth Cady Stanton signature, 1901 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 19)
      Contains signature of Elizabeth Cady Stanton, dated 1901 November 30. Includes certificate of authenticity from Berram & Williams, Booksellers, dated 1999 October 16. Gifted to BJK by Helen Russell.
    - ESPNW BJK ad [removed from frame], circa 2010 (Offsite-box 43, Folder 9)
    - Fort Bragg Special Forces Airborne pencil drawing, 1987 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 6)
      Pencil drawing of soldier presented to BJK by the John F. Kennedy Special Warfare CCenter and School, Fort Bragg, North Carolina.
    - Fortune The Most Powerful Women Opening Night Dinner cloth bag and invitation, 2007 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 20)
    - Independence Hall Documents of Freedom, circa 1990s-2000s (Offsite-box 43, Folder 10)
      Reproductions of the Declaration of Independence, Constitution of the United States, and Bill of Rights from Independence Hall, Philadelphia, PA.
    - Mildred Moffitt watercolor painting, undated (Offsite-box 39, Folder 21)
    - Mildred Moffitt watercolor painting of flower [removed from frame], undated (Offsite-box 43, Folder 11)
    - New Year's Bingo, 2008 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 22)
      Contains Bingo board scoring guide from Fantasy Springs Resort Casino, signed by BJK, Betty Moffitt, and others.
    - Pat Dufry print [removed from frame], 1985 February 10 (Offsite-box 43, Folder 12)
    - Sports, 2000s (Offsite-box 39, Folder 23)
      Contains signed and inscribed baseball cards from Lavonne "Pepper" Paire and Alice "Lefty" Hohlmayer of the All American Girls Professional Baseball League 1943-1954 and commemorative envelope with Arthur Ashe stamp from the World TeamTennis Finals 2005.
    - Sports Illustrated BJK cover [removed from frame], 1973 July 16 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 24)
    - BJK drawing World Tennis Most Significant Player [removed from frame], 1983 (Offsite-box 62)
      Color drawing of BJK and male tennis player with plaque reading "BJK World Tennis Most Significant Player 1953-1983."
    - Tennis Magazine BJK article mounted on board, 1985 January (Offsite-box 59, Folder 4)
    - Framed Shannon Marcus record in tribute of the Challenger 7 astronauts, 1986 (Offsite-box 62)
      Framed record recorded by Shannon Marcus titled "Bid You Goodbye." Framed display also includes photograph of the seven Challenger astronauts, memorial patch, and inscription to BJK from Shannon Marcus.
    - US Open Women's Singles 100th Anniversary frame, 1986 (Offsite-box 62)
      Empty frame engraved with "US Open Tennis Championships 100th Anniversary - Women's Singles 1886-1986."
    - Theatre playbills and tickets, 2006-2018 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 25)
      Contains various tickets and playbills to Broadway and Off-Broadway shows and concerts, as well as signed playbill for Roald Dahl's Willy Wonka at Chicago Shakespeare Theater and tickets and program for BALLS, an Off-Broadway play from the One Year Lease Theatre Company and Stages Repertory Theatre based on the 1973 Battle of the Sexes match.
    - Tickets, 2008-2019 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 26)
      Contains tickets to various events, mostly film showings and sporting events. Events include the 2015 White House Correspondents' Dinner, Elton John concerts at the Beacon Theatre 2010 and Madison Square Garden 2019, the Rocketman (2019) premiere at Lincoln Center, and various sporting events, including Federation Cup matches, Major League Baseball games, and National Hockey League games. Also includes International Tennis Hall of Fame member card. Materials date from 2008-2019.
    - Travel, 1950s-1970s (Offsite-box 39, Folder 27)
      Contains map of South and East England, books of postcards from Moscow, and brochure for the Empire State Building.
    - Vitas Gerulaitis Andy Warhol print reproduction, undated (Offsite-box 57, Folder 15)
    - Wimbledon clippings and photo board, circa 1966 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 1)
    - Wimbledon official program cover and Ladies' Singles bracket page [removed from frame], 1963 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 1)
    - Wimbledon official program Ladies' Singles and Doubles bracket pages mounted display, 1963 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 1)
    - Women's Sports Foundation Do You Know Who I Am? ads [removed from frame], 2002 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 2)
    - Women's Sports Foundation Ilana Kloss certificate [removed from frame], 1998 October 19 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 3)
    - WTA 30th Anniversary photo display [removed from frame], 2003 (Offsite-box 62)
      Originally framed photos with engraved dedication to BJK for the 30th Anniversary of the WTA tour. Removed from frame by conservation.
    - WTA Tour 2007 photo collage (Offsite-box 57, Folder 14)
      Photo collage print on board with plaque text reading "2007 - The Year of Equality: Together We Made History Sony Ericsson WTA Tour."
    - WTT King Trophy watercolor by Janet Nunn [removed from frame], circa 2017 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 4)
    - World Team Tennis Super-tiebreaker magazine cover [removed from frame], 1976 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 5)
    - World Team Tennis Super-tiebreaker magazine cover [removed from frame], 1978 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 13, Item 1)
    - World Tennis magazine cover [removed from frame], 1976 November (Offsite-box 45, Folder 13, Item 2)
      Cover features the World TeamTennis champions team The New York Sets, including BJK.
  - Subseries VII.F. Posters, 1970-2019
    Subseries VII.F contains all posters in the collection, including event posters, advertisement posters, and political posters and signs. Notable items include poster for the BJK Invitational 1971 of the Virginia Slims National Pro Circuit, advertisement posters for Nike and American Express featuring BJK, and a poster for an Original 9 reunion signed by all nine players. Items date from the 1970s to 2019.
    Items are arranged chronologically.
    - Advertisements/ BJK Endorsements, 1970s-2008 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 1)
      Contains BJK Carnation instant breakfast ad poster and several American Express posters featuring BJK.
    - BJK Invitational, 1971 January 14-17 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 1)
      Poster for the BJK Invitational in Long Beach, California, the second tournament of the Virginia Slims National Pro Circuit.
    - The Virginia Slims National Indoor Championships, circa 1970s (Offsite-box 58, Folder 3)
    - Bobby Riggs Memorial Bake Sale, circa 1975 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 1)
      Poster for event sponsored by the Princeton Seminary Women Men's Auxiliary of the Princeton Theological Seminary.
    - San Francisco Giants, 1977 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 2)
      Poster of full team roster, including BJK's brother, pitcher Randy Moffitt.
    - Inside Women's Tennis U.S. Open, 1978 September 13 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 2)
      Inside Women's Tennis poster from publication reading "An Era Ends The First Ten Years of the U.S. Open" with images of past champions.
    - Nike Long May She Reign BJK ad, circa 1980s (Offsite-box 61, Folder 4)
      Includes two copies of poster, one on board.
    - Virginia Slims, 1986 March (Offsite-box 59, Folder 3)
      Virginia Slims World Championship Series poster mounted on board with text "To BJK for Shaping the Future of Women's Tennis. From Virginia Slims."
    - Virginia Slims Legends AmFAR benefit, 1994 March 19-20 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 2)
      Poster for Virginia Slims Legends Presents The Greatest Hits of Our Time... In Concert And On the Court benefiting American Foundation for AIDS Research. Concert featuring Liza Minnelli hosted by Angela Lansbury and Pro-Celebrity and Lgends Challenge. Poster signed by Minnelli and Lansbury, as well as BJK and additional Legends players.
    - Virginia Slims Legends On the Courts and in Concert, 1995 April 7-9 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 2)
      Poster for Virginia Slims Legends Hit It, Ladies On the Courts and In Concert benefit for the National AIDS Fund. Signed by BJK and additional Legends players.
    - Fed Cup World Team Final, 1999 September 18-19 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 2)
      Poster for the Fed Cup World Team Final USA vs. Russia match held at the Taube Family Tennis Stadium, Stanford University. Signed by BJK and team.
    - American Express BJK ad subway signs, 2000 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 3)
    - The Concert for New York City, 2001 October 20 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 2)
      Signed to BJK and Ilana Kloss by Melissa Etheridge, Mick Jagger, Elton John, and Paul McCartney.
    - BJK 60th birthday, 2003 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 5)
      Poster signed with birthday messages.
    - Sri Chinmoy Happiness, 2003 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 3)
      Signed and inscribed with personal note by Sri Chinmoy to BJK.
    - US Open 25th Anniversary, 2003 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 6)
      Signed by BJK.
    - WTT 30th anniversary season, 2005 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 3)
      Eight copies of WTT 30th season anniversary poster signed by players.
    - HBO BJK: Portrait of a Pioneer, 2006 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 7)
    - HBO BJK: Portrait of a Pioneer, 2006 (Oversize OS-large)
    - US Open, 2006 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 6)
      Signed with notes of congratulations to BJK for renaming of USTA BJK National Tennis Center.
    - Hillary Clinton 2008 campaign, 2007 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 3)
      Three green and yellow signs for the HRC 2008 Presidential Campaign. Signs read "TURN UP THE HEAT" on one side and "TURN AMERICA AROUND" on other.
    - Girleffect.org, circa 2010 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 8)
    - Title IX, circa 2010 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 2)
      Title IX "I exercise my rights" poster featuring BJK.
    - STL Today Sports page, 2011 July 3 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 3)
      Article titled "Three Aces" highlighted, a story on tennis players Carol Hanks Aucamp, Justina Bricka, and Mary Ann Eisel Beattie. Handwritten note from Justina to BJK wishing BJK a happy 70th birthday.
    - Original 9 Reunion, 2012 April 5-8 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 2)
      Poster from the WTA and Family Circle Cup for the Reunion of the Original 9: Founding Members of the Tour. Poster signed by all nine members.
    - Kaye Ballard Live on Stage, 2014 March 11 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 3)
      Signed by Kaye Ballard.
    - Harlem Junior Tennis and Education Program, circa 2015 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 2)
      Signed by members of the program.
    - Hillary Clinton Stronger Together, 2016 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 2)
      Two identical blue posters/ signs reading "STRONGER TOGETHER" from HRC's 2016 Presidential Campaign.
    - Battle of the Sexes film, 2017 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 2)
      Several posters for the 2017 Battle of the Sexes film. One poster signed by BJK.
    - Salesforce Equality Trailblazers, 2017 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 2)
      Salesforce Equality Awards poster featuring BJK, Lilly Ledbetter, Patricia Arquette, and Mary J. Blige as Equality Trailblazers.
    - March for Our Lives, 2018 March 24 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 2)
    - US Open Pride, 2019 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 6)
    - WTT, 2019 (Offsite-box 61, Folder 8)
- Series VIII. Photographs, 1935-2020; 10 Linear feet in 6.5 record cartons, 2 flat boxes, and oversize folders
  Series VIII includes photographs, negatives, and slides from throughout BJK's life and career. Subjects of photos include BJK's childhood and family, youth tennis matches, professional tennis matches and events, TeamTennis and World TeamTennis events, notable people in BJK's life, and various public appearances, events, and fundraisers attended by BJK. Notable photo groups include BJK's childhood and family photos, various Wimbledon matches, TeamTennis league photos and slides, and BJK receiving the Presidential Medal of Freedom from President Barack Obama. Materials date from 1935 to 2019.
  Subseries VIII.A. Childhood and family
  Subseries VIII.B. Career
  Subseries VIII.C. TeamTennis
  Subseries VIII.D. Events
  Subseries VIII.E. People
  Subseries VIII.F. Slides
  Additional photographs are located in Series II. Albums. Additional photographs selected by the curator and conservators to remain framed are located in Series X. Artifacts and memorabilia.
  - Subseries VIII.A. Childhood and family, 1935-2010; 0.5 Linear feet in 1 record carton
    Subseries VIII.A contains photographs of BJK during her childhood and adolescence, photographs of her immediate family throughout their lives, and photographs of additional relatives. BJK's baby photos include formal portraits and family candids. Childhood photographs include BJK with parents and brother Randy and with classmates. A group of photographs originally in frames have been removed for conservation purposes and are described accordingly. Photos date from 1935 to 2010.
    Photographs are grouped by family members, starting with BJK's baby and childhood photos, followed by photographs of her parents and brother, and finally Moffitt and Jerman family relatives.
    Additional family photographs selected by the curator and conservators to remain framed are located in Series X. Artifacts and memorabilia.
    - Baby photos, 1943-1948 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 7)
    - Childhood family, 1943-1955 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 8)
      Photos of young BJK, parents, and brother Randy.
    - Childhood, 1948-1958 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 9)
      Contains photos of BJK's childhood and adolesence, including photos with classmates and formal class and school club photos.
    - Childhood [oversized], 1955-1961 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 1)
      Contains photo of BJK on tennis court with another youth player and formal headshot composition of BJK and members of the Zayn service sorority.
    - Childhood and relatives [oversized], 1955-1958 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 1)
      Includes formal photos of BJK's school class dances and color photo of unidentified relative.
    - BJK and parents, 1950-2005 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 10)
    - Betty Moffitt, 1935-1995 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 11)
    - Bill Moffitt, 1940-1990 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 12)
    - Bill and Betty Moffitt (2 folders), 1940-2000 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 13-14)
    - Randy Moffitt, 1960-1990 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 15)
    - Moffitt and Jerman relatives (5 folders), circa 1930-2010 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 16-20)
    - Family [oversized], circa 1940s-1950s (Offsite-box 57, Folder 2)
    - Family photos removed from frames, circa 1940-1980 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 21)
      Contains Moffitt family photos removed from frames by the Conservation Department, including photos of Bill Moffitt, and photo of Bill and Betty Moffitt.
  - Subseries VIII.B. Career, 1955-2005; 1.5 Linear feet in 2 record cartons